RG 074:058, Ancestry of Captain Lawrence C. Howard
Connecticut State Library
Ancestry of Captain Lawrence C. Howard
1936-1959
Connecticut State Library
DeMott, John J.
1.25 cubic feet
Seven notebooks of genealogical material dealing with the Howard family.
RG074_058
2002-050
Scope and Content
Seven notebooks of genealogical material on the Howard family. Includes genealogical charts, correspondence, and photostat copies of genealogical notes.
Related Material
Howard family: History and Genealogy Unit Special Genealogical File, 1936-1987, Connecticut State Library
Index Terms
Persons:
DeMott, John J
Family Names:
Howard family
Places:
Connecticut -- Genealogy
Document Types:
Genealogical tables; Correspondence; Genealogies
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Provenance
The papers came to the Connecticut State Library in July 1960 from John J. DeMott.
Container List
- Ancestry of Captain Lawrence C. Howard, 1936-1959
  Titles under each volume are taken from the tabs in the notebooks.
  - Volume 1 (Box 1)
    - Howard (Box 1)
    - Howard, Parkhurst Manuscript, Hartford (Box 1)
    - Howard, Hempstead Diary, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Jones, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Howard - Misc., 1947-1958 (Box 1)
    - Late correspondence, important, 1954-1958 (Box 1)
    - Book, Edward Sewall, 1956-1958 (Box 1)
    - L.C. Howard obituary, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Charts (Box 1)
  - Volume 2 (Box 1)
    - Lawrence Clayton Howard, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Charts (Box 1)
    - Revolutionary (Box 1)
    - 1812, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Sources of Information in Connecticut, 1933 January, photostat copy (Box 1)
    - Beckwith family, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Chapman family, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Wakeman family, 1954-1959 (Box 1)
    - Bushnell family (Box 1)
    - Brooks family, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Hungerford family (Box 1)
  - Volume 3 (Box 1)
    - Sons of the Revolution, 1947-1948 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut in the Revolution, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Eliphalet Holmes pension, 1948-1954 (Box 1)
    - Eliphalet Holmes, other, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Holmes family, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Colonel Samuel Selden, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Selden Family (Box 1)
    - Warner family (Box 1)
    - Jonathan Warner (Box 1)
    - Selden Warner, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Elias Tully pension (Box 1)
    - Elias Tully, other (Box 1)
    - Tully family, 1954-1958 (Box 1)
    - John Tully's Almanac (Box 1)
      There are no papers on this subject.
  - Volume 4 (Box 2)
    - Congdon, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Maynard, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Brewster, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Coit, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Douglas, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Keeney, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Lee (Leigh) (Box 2)
    - Manwaring, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Miner, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Mould (Box 2)
    - Palmer (Box 2)
    - Raymond, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Turner, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Dart, 1949-1955 (Box 2)
  - Volume 5 (Box 2)
    - Gates, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Andrews family, 1948 (Box 2)
    - Kirby family (Box 2)
    - Marvin family, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Clark family, 1954 (Box 2)
    - Ely family, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Maverick family, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Fuller family (Box 2)
    - Fuller, Mayflower descent, 1948-1949 (Box 2)
    - Kirtland family (Box 2)
    - Champion Family, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Peck family, 1936-1954 (Box 2)
    - Brainard family (Box 2)
    - Olmstead family, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Volume 6 (Box 2)
    - Kelley, 1949-1953 (Box 2)
  - Volume 7 (Box 3)
    - Perkins, 1950-1957 (Box 3)
    - Kelley - Perkins - Chapman, 1949-1954 (Box 3)